THE FILM "PARAXNORMAL"
IS A WORK OF FICTION.
IT CONTAINS SUPERNATURAL ELEMENTS, CRIME,
AND SOME LEWD AND VIOLENT SCENES
THAT MAY BE SENSITIVE TO SOME VIEWERS.
WE GREATLY APPRECIATE
THE VIEWERS' CONSIDERATION.
BOY WANTED BY POLICE
ANY INFORMATION LEADING TO HIS ARREST
WILL BE REWARDED
-Help!
Help!
Run!
What are we going to do now?
Calm down, everyone.
Don't be afraid.
We are boys.
We must live without fear.
My mom said that
when we're in danger,
we should recite prayers.
-Really?
-Yes.
What? Don't you believe it?
Come on. Let's recite prayers.
There's a squirrel--
That's dikir barat, not a prayer.
Up.
-Lailahailla anta subhanaka inni
-kuntu minazzolimin.
There's nothing. Can you see it?
I don't see it. Do you see it, Fatih?
I don't see anything. Do you, Yasin?
I don't see anything either.
-Do you see anything?
-I do.
Who wants to be cut first?
-Mom!
Yasin, you're amazing.
You didn't cry at all.
Right. Out of the four of us,
you're the bravest, Yasin.
Come on. That's enough.
It's just a little.
He's not going to cut it all off.
It's painful, you know?
Painful?
That's normal.
My mom says pain,
if endured, becomes a hill.
Suffer now, enjoy later.
Every pain we experience in life
will make life easier later.
No pain, no gain.
Someday, we will grow up and succeed.
We will succeed!
-Help!
-It hurts!
30 YEARS LATER
Thank you all for coming.
Why did you call us here?
Do you know how much I'm losing
by being here?
I lose 3,000 rials every hour.
Old friends are like this.
You must want us to join
a multi-level marketing scheme, right?
Or insurance or water filters, right?
Actually, I want to ask for your help.
How much do you need? Tell me.
One million? Two million?
Three million? Say the number.
Be patient.
You can call us for help.
We can transfer it to you.
He's right.
-But why here?
-That's right, man.
We're wearing like this
in this hot weather.
At least take us to a hotel
in Dubai, Sydney, or Paris.
This isn't up to our standards.
This is our place.
We remember where we fell,
let alone where we used to play.
You were the one who fell. We're fine.
Hey.
Hey!
Look at the time. It's already late.
I have to do makeup
at the house next door.
Hey, bro.
Hurry up!
I need to be quick.
I have to drop off my boss's car.
Who's that?
He rented it.
He rented everything.
The car and the driver.
And you, Yasin.
The bodyguards, the car, and your clothes.
And Fat…
You brought a helicopter to impress us?
All sorts of things.
I know the truth.
You knew?
You may not look clever,
but you're smart now.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Hey, my boss!
You should say congratulations
to me, boss.
Because our sales made
a profit of 100,000.
Say congratulations. Say it.
Congratulations, my foot.
I told you to sell the goods in the truck,
not the truck itself.
Is this your son?
My goodness.
Open your mouth.
It's full of rust.
I'm going to spray water into his mouth.
Hey.
Now gargle.
-Hey, what are you doing?
-Gargle!
Come here.
What are you doing?
Boss, I'm washing them.
Come here.
What is it, boss?
Are you crazy? They're our customers.
I know, but I'm going to wash them.
You told me to wash dirty things
in the shop.
Right?
Wait. Can you blink for me?
Boss, you look terrible.
Boss, people secrete from their bottoms.
Why are you secreting from your eyes?
Hey, get out now.
Why do I have to go out?
Get out now.
I don't want to see your face.
I'm just doing my job, boss.
Before I wash your brain,
you'd better leave now.
But I'm just doing my job, boss.
Scram!
Hey, all of you, get out!
Hey, kid.
Come here.
Yes, I'm talking to you.
Yes, boss.
If you want to sell things,
do it properly.
Don't deceive people. Be honest.
Relax. What's the matter?
Yesterday, I bought a dress
for 200 ringgit.
When I got home,
I saw that the shirt was torn.
Calm down. May I see it?
-That's the plastic.
-Sorry.
It's normal for bundle items to be torn.
They're often damaged.
Before I tear your face apart,
you'd better refund my money.
Calm down.
The truth is,
this tear isn't just any tear.
The one who tore this shirt is Hulk Hogan.
It's a limited edition.
Hey, before I turn into Hulk Hogan,
you'd better refund my money.
Refund it!
Hurry up!
I've come a long way.
-Be patient.
-Sir, please be patient.
Calm down. Yasin.
He doesn't understand
that this shirt is a limited edition.
You're giving me a headache, Yasin.
I'm firing you today.
With triple talaq!
My goodness.
-You knew?
-Yes.
I regret wearing this shirt.
This cigar is made from durian stems.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed.
I feel bad hearing your stories.
Actually, I'm not really struggling.
I have a house, four cars,
and a side business.
And I know you guys
are having a hard time.
That's why I asked you to come here.
It's because I want to help you.
Wait a minute.
Are you out of your mind?
You know we're struggling
and you're asking for our help?
-You're really asking for it.
-How bold.
No.
You guys are struggling
and I need your help,
so I want you to join my plan.
What do you want us to do?
What's the plan, man?
-It's a plan to make us millionaires.
-What?
Be true, man.
What kind of millionaire?
-I don't understand. Be direct.
-What…
What do you mean?
We're going to rob a place.
-My goodness.
-Sorry, man. It's not me, man.
-Come on. No.
-Don't be surprised.
-This is a wrong and forbidden act.
-Oh my god. No, man.
Oh my god. No.
-I don't want to do that.
-Hear me out first.
-No.
-All the wealth I have now
came from robberies.
Thank goodness… What?
From robberies?
No way you're asking us to do that.
This time, I really need
your help with the robbery.
You got rich because of those robberies.
That's your business.
You can force me, but I refuse to do it.
-Right.
-This is wrong.
-You do your business. We do ours.
-Please.
But there's ten million in that villa.
Where is it?
Yasin, what's wrong with you?
You didn't invite me.
Come on. Can I follow you all?
But listen to my explanation first.
This thing is neither easy nor difficult.
Neither easy nor difficult?
The easy part is yours.
The difficult part is mine.
The villa is on a hill,
far from other residential areas
and close to the forest.
A family died in that house long ago
and the case remains unsolved.
People say the deceased left
a treasure chest there.
And in that chest,
there are gold bars and cash
worth nearly ten million ringgit.
No one dares to go near that house
because it's said to be haunted.
Guys.
Hey, Yasin.
I want to ask you something.
Are you going to the villa?
When it comes to this, you know me.
When it comes to ten million,
I have no issue, so I'm in.
That's right.
But the problem is, I'm scared.
That villa is scary.
Hey, let's just change the plan.
Why don't we rob
Mr. Dolah's house instead?
Mr. Dolah is…
We can do it.
Does he even have money?
-He does, right?
-Hey.
-What's wrong with you?
-What?
-Mr. Dolah is my dad.
-So what?
What's the problem? His issue is his.
We deal with our own. We're a team.
-Teamwork.
-Yes.
You have a point.
But he is my dad. Jeez.
Dad will always be a dad.
Then he'll end up dead too.
RIP. Yes.
Seriously, guys.
Do you want to rob it or not?
So?
How many times do you have to ask?
What's the point of us
gathering together like this?
Of course we're here to rob.
So what's the problem now?
Ghosts, jinns, demons, devils?
What are you worried about?
Compared to them, we're nobler.
Come on.
What's my name? Yasin.
My parents are great. They named me Yasin.
Since my name is Yasin,
ghosts can't harm or look at me.
They'll tremble with fear.
-That's my man.
-My man.
Water ghosts? I'll drown them.
Oh my god.
-Your god is also my god. Come on!
-Yeah.
You'll drown them? You can't even swim.
Swimming is different.
Don't use that as an example.
So?
That's why I need friends
who are brave like you guys.
-Including me?
-Yes.
Let's start.
-Okay then.
-Okay.
Can we reconsider this?
Blood in blood arms, brother.
Come on, brotherhood.
-Come on.
If that's the case, come on.
-Okay.
Three, four!
ASFATRIYAS!
Say it with me.
-What's that?
-What does that even mean?
AS for Anas.
FAT for Fatih.
RI for Asri.
YAS for Yasin.
ASFATRIYAS.
-Fine.
-Okay.
ASFATRIFAK.
-Come on.
Three, four!
-ASFATRIYAS!
-Okay.
-It doesn't sound as nice.
Enough.
-We'll check the place tomorrow.
-Yes, come on.
-It's too late. We need to sleep.
-Right. Let's sleep.
You go first.
It's up to you.
Sleep early, Yasin.
We have a lot to do tomorrow.
Where
Will I find
I'm crying
Anas, you scared me.
What's wrong? You look pale
like a dead person.
I'm not feeling well.
If you're not well, get some rest.
Why are you still up?
This place is full of spirits
and you're alone here.
Hard things will become soft
when the time comes.
The same goes otherwise.
Soft things will become hard
when the time comes.
What do you mean?
If a glass of water
can quench your thirst,
why ask for an ocean to drown in?
-Just for fun
-Singing by the roadside
-Dancing, even if it's not real dangdut
-What matters is the groove, it's fun
-Singing, even if it's not real dangdut
-What matters is we can be happy
-One more time!
-Just for fun
Singing by the roadside
Just for fun
Dancing
Let's go.
The cutter.
I don't know what to say.
What else do you want to say?
Usually Yasin would have something
to say in this situation.
Say a few words, Yasin.
-Up!
-A cutter. I need it to cut this chain.
He needs a cutter, Yasin.
It's a cutter.
But where's the house? I can't see it.
It's on the hill.
Why build a house so far from the gate?
-I don't feel good.
-You do it.
This place is like…
I don't think we should do this.
We're already here.
I have a bad feeling.
Come on.
Let's come again next time.
We're already here.
Enough.
-Let's go.
-Here, Fat.
I have goosebumps.
Are we seriously going in?
Have you thought about it carefully?
We're already here.
Look at all these dry leaves.
Fat, don't leave me.
Fat. Anas.
Hey, Yasin.
-I don't want to go in.
-What are you doing, man? Come on, man.
-I don't want to!
-Don't be scared, man.
-Police! They're forcing me to rob!
-Hey, we want to…
We want to rob.
Why are you calling the police?
-Come on.
-Okay.
-Scouts, Red Crescent, JKKK. Please help!
-Come on.
-I don't want to. I'm scared.
-I'll help. Come on. Get out, man.
It feels eerie.
I'm getting goosebumps.
It's cool, man.
It's giving me chills.
Easy.
This house looks easy to break into.
There's nobody inside, right? Let's go.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
To be a great robber like me,
you need mental and physical training.
What do you mean, man?
We're already…
He's right. Let's not become robbers.
Let's just be crocodiles.
I told you this place isn't right.
Let's go.
Fat, hurry up and get in the car.
Nas, let's go back. Come on.
Let's go back.
Start the car.
Hurry up.
Come on. I don't feel good.
Hurry up!
Can you stuff leaves or something
in his mouth? He's so noisy! Gosh.
Reverse the car quickly.
I'm really getting goosebumps.
A dream house.
This is the floor plan of the villa
we're going to enter.
Okay, it has many doors.
Many doors, many paths.
But it only leads to one path.
Hey, that sounds familiar.
But we'll go in through…
the front door.
The front door?
If we use the front door,
we have to greet them.
"Peace be upon you.
We're here to rob you."
Yasin, stop fooling around.
Be serious. I'm focusing here.
The proper way to rob is
to break in through the back,
go onto the roof, and dig the ground.
That's the right way to do it.
No one uses the front door.
You say it like you know everything.
You talk like you've done this before.
You've probably only stolen small change.
Of course, there's only a small change.
It was from the mosque donation box.
There were no big bills.
But if you steal from the mosque
donation box, it's not blessed.
Put blessings aside. Let's focus on this.
-It's important to know our entry point.
-Okay.
Focus. Be serious, okay?
We enter through the front door.
-The front door.
-And when we enter…
It sounds close.
Thank goodness. He's dead.
-Problem solved.
-So it's just the three of us.
-For now.
-Yes.
Eat slowly.
You're eating greedily.
Gosh. Hey.
Slowly, Fat.
Hey, Fat. Eat slowly.
All right, everyone.
This is how you become
a professional robber.
Stamina is important.
Let me ask you just one thing, Nas.
The house we're going to rob…
The place is eerie. It's haunted.
-What if--
-What's wrong with you?
You and ghost stories.
How many times must I tell you?
No matter what ghost it is,
they won't be able to harm us.
-That's right, man.
-Shut up.
Don't interrupt me.
Remember. I said it many times.
No matter what ghost it is,
they won't be able to harm us.
I'm okay
with those kinds of things, Yasin.
But right now, we're moving as a team.
We know the slowest one is this guy.
You can tell his level of thinking
by the way he eats.
He's only good at eating.
He's slow at everything else.
That's the problem.
You're right.
I am right.
At least we're making preparations.
So tonight,
we'll prepare ourselves mentally.
-Is there more?
-Yes.
How?
I told you. It's him. There's nobody else.
Yasin.
Fat.
What are we doing here?
How much longer
do we have to stay here, Yasin?
Quiet. Be patient.
-I'm scared, Yasin.
-Be patient.
I want to water the flowers
at my mom's house, Yasin.
That's your mom's business.
It's our business, so don't mix it up.
I'm here, and Fat is here too.
We'll wait until Anas comes to pick us up.
Focus!
Yasin, I smell stink beans.
We've been sitting here for a while.
There are all sorts of smells.
It's really stinky, Yasin.
Enough, man. Enough.
What's the matter, man?
Let's move.
Move over. He wants to pass through.
Let him pass through.
Let him pass.
-Don't look.
-I can't.
That hurts!
Is that Anas's spirit?
-Not yet, but he'll be one soon.
-Not yet.
Hey, help me out!
You jerk!
Hey, help me out.
I've been waiting for you
this whole time, you know?
We've been waiting for you
and you act like this?
My heart almost stopped.
I'm so annoyed!
You're driving me crazy, you know that?
But you feel motivated, right?
Motivated?
If it were up to me, I'd dig a hole here
and bury you alive.
Let me explain.
He's the weakest one.
It's not just his spirit.
Even his libido is weak.
Why did you do this to us?
What's going on?
Yes, now I'm turning into a ghost
just looking at your face.
How dare you, man?
Hey, even if I become a ghost,
I won't be a shrouded ghost.
I'll just be normal.
I want to be friends with you guys.
I don't care.
Hey, why does it smell bad here?
We're sweating. That's why it smells like…
No, it really smells like a corpse.
Nas, did you bring a friend along?
-Where?
-Here.
Why is he wearing lipstick
around his eyes?
I came alone.
-Are you sure?
-I came alone.
If you came alone…
Untie this for me.
Right now, you deal with your problem.
We'll deal with ours. You're on your own.
Goodbye, brother.
-Hey, help me! Untie me. Hey!
-Let's go.
Help me.
Yasin.
I'm scared.
Help…
What about me?
Yasin.
Help me.
Yasin!
Guys!
Hey!
Hey, you have so many cars.
Which one is this?
Well, you know I am rich.
You can take it after this.
Are you serious?
You guys don't have a car, right?
That's a good idea.
It's unbelievable.
He's giving away his car
like giving away a bag of chips.
Exactly.
Hey, where are we going?
We're going to enter the villa.
What? Now?
-No--
-Are you serious, Nas? I'm not ready yet.
No, we need protection
to enter the villa. Okay?
So I want to take all of us
to meet someone.
-Who is it?
-Who?
Raja Dukun.
Who's that?
Hey.
I feel like I'm being pulled.
-Control yourself. Pull back.
-Stay back.
Thank goodness.
Enough.
Let's go in.
-Now?
-Yes.
You're brave, right?
Go ahead.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Peace--
Up!
Peace be upon you, sir.
Peace be upon you too.
Let Yasin handle this.
How do you know?
Trust me.
Don't be afraid.
It's just a subtle game.
Someone must have not taken
the obligatory bath.
Right?
So that's why you looked so happy
in the bathroom yesterday.
Nonsense.
Let's go down and check.
We showered together yesterday. Get out.
But you were the happiest.
No.
Let's check each other.
Get inside.
See.
Okay. It's smooth.
Nothing happened.
Look at me.
I told you. It was him.
Murni, Mira, Umi, Sharifah.
Go play outside.
Sir?
Who are you talking to?
You will never understand.
Only certain people can talk to them.
You can't see them. I can.
We have to make friends in this world.
Otherwise, you'll feel lonely.
Your daughters are so beautiful.
Hey.
Can you see them?
I was just trying to please him.
He's pleasing him.
Very subtle.
What's your name?
My name is Asri, sir.
Asri.
So can you recite "Surah Al-'Asr"?
"Surah Al-'Asr"? Yes, sir.
Bismillahir rahmanir raheem.
Wal 'asr. Innal insa na la fi khusr.
Illallazi na amanu wa'amilus solihati
watawa saubil haq watawa saubis sabr.
Saubis sabr.
My name is Anas.
Okay, recite "Surah An-Nas."
Bismillahir rahmanir raheem.
Qul a'udzu birabbbin nas.
Mali kin nas. Ilahin nas.
Min sharril was wasil khan nas.
Alladzi yuwas wisu fi sudhu rin nas.
Minal jinna tiwan nas.
Good.
You. What's your name?
My name Fatih.
"Al-Fatihah."
Bismillahir rahmanir raheem.
Alhamdulillahi rabbil 'alamin.
Arrahmanirrahim.
Maliki yau middin.
Iyya kana' buduwa iyya kanasta'in.
Ihdinassirotol mustaqim.
Sirotolladzi na'an'amta 'alaihim.
Ghoiril maghdhu bi'alaihim waladhollin.
-Amen.
And you?
I'm talking to you.
Do you seriously want
to know his name, sir?
Yasin.
But people call me…
Qulhuwallahu ahad.
Allahussamad.
Lam yalid walam yulad.
Walam yaqullahu kufuwan ahad.
Beautiful.
Hey.
What's your purpose in meeting me?
To change our lives.
We want to get rich.
Do you want to play the lottery?
Do you want to get rich quickly?
Do foreign exchange. Gambling. Everything.
-No.
-That's not the way to get rich.
No, we're not trying to gamble
or anything like that.
We want to rob a villa.
What?
We just want to rob.
That's not my job.
I can't help you guys with this.
It's nonsense. Do your own job.
How will the Malays progress?
The Malays only wail.
Crying here and there.
They never learn to plunder.
That's all they know.
But that villa has ten million.
Where is it?
But that place is haunted, sir.
Hey, I'm the king of all the kings
when it comes to ghosts.
Put that aside.
You do your job. I'll do mine.
Is it not superstitious?
Put that aside.
Thirty percent.
Twenty-five?
-Yes.
-Let's try.
-Twenty-five.
-Take it or leave it.
-Twenty-five, sir.
-Twenty-five?
Up!
Is this allowed?
-Are you serious?
-Put it aside.
Again?
Where's the water?
Sir.
Now I understand why you look healthy.
At your age,
you should just be in memories.
I get it now.
You don't drink sweet drinks.
I tried it earlier.
Even though the water was bitter,
I tried to finish it for my health.
Why did you drink horse urine?
This is horse urine.
-Horse urine?
-Yes.
-Listen here.
-This is your fault, Yasin.
Here.
Don't move.
-Where is he? Sir?
-Sir?
-He is gone!
-Sir!
-Sir, don't leave us!
Hey, why are you guys so loud?
We're here to rob.
Good thing I wasn't too loud!
I think I know that animal.
That doesn't sound good.
Is he all right in there?
Stop joking around.
Listen.
Wherever you are,
either between the doors or the walls,
come out.
Come out now.
Is he handling the ghosts
or being bullied by them?
What do you think, Yasin?
What do you think, man?
I feel like I want to beat you up.
I'm innocent.
The four kids outside are guilty.
I have nothing to do with this.
Trust me.
This is the first and the last time
I'm doing something like this.
Come on.
-He won.
-Yeah.
Great.
All of you can go in now.
I've handled everything,
including big and small things.
You can go in.
The world is about to cry, kids.
I'm shaking
"The world is crying"? "I'm shaking"?
What does it mean?
-Yasin.
-The ghost is scared of him.
He's good.
What does "the world is crying" mean?
That's his business.
-His business is his. We do ours.
-Yes.
-Can we rob now?
-Okay, my bra.
Bra, my foot. That's for women. Say "bro."
Okay, man. My bad. You go first.
Ready?
Up!
Yasin.
We're about to rob.
Do we really need to say a prayer?
Put that aside.
Isn't it "amen"?
Yasin, I'm right behind you.
All the way back.
Hey, don't go too far.
Yasin.
Be careful, Yasin.
Hey.
Don't go too far.
What kind of place is this?
There are so many shrouds.
This isn't an ordinary house.
It's a corpse house.
Silence.
Hey, the door closed by itself!
-We're trapped.
-Hey.
-Close his mouth.
-Quiet!
-Don't do that. No, please. Don't do that.
-I'll do this.
-Why did the door close by itself?
-He's our friend.
-Why did--
-We've arrived.
What has arrived?
What are we going to do now?
Don't worry.
Be silent.
Who is that?
-Be quiet.
-Who is that?
I was just about to ask.
Who's in that picture?
That's the owner of the house who died.
-The owner of the house?
-The owner of the house.
We're going to take their treasure.
Relax.
Owners.
We apologize for coming like this.
Allow us to take your treasure.
It's better to let us handle it
than to leave it as it is.
Yasin, don't play around
with things like this.
Enough, Yasin.
Let's find the treasure chest now.
Then let's get out of this house.
-I'm scared.
-Okay, guys.
-Okay.
-I'm asking for permission.
Guys.
-I got one idea.
-What?
I think I should stay outside
and you three go inside.
Okay.
Anything happen,
don't call the police, right?
You want to go outside?
You go to hell by bus.
-Nonsense.
-We're here already. Just follow us.
You were trying to escape, huh?
Nas, which way?
To the right.
Where?
-To the right.
-Come.
-Hey.
Hey. Don't go too fast, man.
What is this place?
There are white cloths everywhere.
It feels eerie. Aren't you scared?
Why did I become friends with you guys?
We shouldn't separate.
We must stick together.
The lamp is so nice.
Fat. Where's Fat?
-What?
-Where's Fat?
Fat.
He was behind here.
Is Fat dead?
I'm here.
Guys, come. I found it. Come.
What is it?
A chest.
I found the chest.
I found it. Look.
Look.
Applause.
Good job, son.
Just because stupid is free,
you want to have it all.
We're looking for a safe,
not a refrigerator.
Even if you're dumb,
don't trouble others. Understand?
-Yes.
-Do you really want to get in here?
Hey, Fat.
Do you even know
what this refrigerator is for?
When you die,
we'll chop you into eight pieces
and keep them in the refrigerator
to freeze your meat.
That's what this refrigerator is for.
Just joking, man. Just joking.
Use your brain.
I'm scared, Yasin.
-Stay with me.
-Yeah.
We need to relax.
Nas, you go that side.
What about me?
You're with me. Let's move forward. Okay?
-All right. Walk.
-Let's go, man.
I'll search here first.
-Hey, wait. Don't push me.
-Yasin.
What room is this, Yasin?
Where do I need to look, Yasin?
-Where should I look?
-Go search around over there.
It's not here.
-Look for it.
-Okay, I'll look for it.
None.
-My goodness!
-Yasin!
-What…
-I can't, Yasin.
I'm about to pee my pants, Yasin.
Go.
Let's go together, Yasin.
We can't pee together.
You've seen mine
since we were kids, Yasin.
But it's different now that we're grown.
Just go.
Promise you won't go far.
Okay. I'll wait.
-Promise?
-Yes.
I won't close the door, okay?
Yeah, I'm here.
They're still here.
Be gone!
What are you looking for? Find the safe.
Yasin.
One
Eternal love
Three
Hunger and thirst
Her nails are polished
Her face has been made up
Signs of a radiant bride
Someone touched my hand!
What are you doing, man?
I was just playing with you.
-Have you found anything yet?
-No.
Hey, come on.
This room? This…
We can't stay chill with things like this.
It's not fair if I open the door,
let's play rock paper scissors.
All right, man. We're fine. Let's go, man.
-Rock paper scissors.
-Okay, one more.
-Okay.
We did the same.
Rock paper scissors.
-We did the same.
-Same.
Rock paper scissors.
It's the same again. Let's go back.
Nothing's changed anyway.
Last one.
-Rock paper scissors.
Relax. You need to keep calm
in a situation like this.
This means I win.
So you three have to open the door.
No man. Yours is turned around like this.
You must open the door.
Hey, Yasin. It's three against one.
It's obvious you've lost, Yasin.
-Yeah, man.
-Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
-So?
-How?
How?
There's nothing inside there.
Let's try looking in another room.
-What's wrong?
-It's nothing. Enough. Forget it.
-Forget it.
-Don't lie.
-No, that room is empty. There's nothing.
Hey.
Fat, don't bother opening that door.
This is my house!
You can't escape.
Why has she gone silent?
She's gone.
Turn that off.
She might notice us.
You…
I think she's gone.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go. Go.
Who's that, Yasin? Who is it?
-Where?
-She's back there.
Let's go.
Where do we go, Yasin?
Fat, what are you doing?
I'm pretending to be a wall.
-I can see you.
-Really?
Use your brain. What were you thinking?
I've seen how dumb you are
since you were young.
-Hurry. Go in.
-Let's go under this table.
Here, Fat.
I'm scared. I don't want to die here.
She's coming.
Where?
We're not under the table.
Why did you say that?
She heard it. She believes it.
Guys, what are you doing there?
Run. Run for your life. Run!
Fat, what's wrong with you?
How many of us came?
One, little two, little three.
Is someone behind me?
Yasin.
Anas.
Asri.
My goodness!
Where should we hide?
-Where?
-Where do we hide?
Help!
Kick her!
Yasin, don't go too fast.
Is she dead?
-I don't know.
-Yasin, wait up.
Is that her?
Yasin, what if she wakes up?
What will we do then?
Check on her, Yasin.
Okay.
Nas, over here.
You need to keep calm
in a situation like this.
-Keep calm.
-We have to…
What are you going to do, Yasin?
Where is her face?
-Her face?
-She has no face.
Relax.
Turn her around.
Is that a song title? "Turn Around."
You listen to too many songs.
Careful, Yasin. She might bite you.
What's that, Yasin?
Yasin! Her eyes.
Her eyes are blinking rapidly.
Her eyes.
You need to keep calm
in a situation like this.
She blinks rapidly because she's a mix.
I know it.
-A mix?
-What?
-What kind of mix?
-A Cimak mix.
Cimak?
-What's that?
-Chinese mom, Mamak dad.
Is that true?
Okay. Why is she blinking?
Why?
She fainted differently.
We call it…
Maktam Bel Bella Art.
What's that?
Eyes wide open but blinking.
-It's a thing.
-Is it?
But if she's blinking, she's fine.
Not when her eyes are closed.
You should be scared.
It's okay.
What are you going to do now?
-Hey.
-Hey, Yasin!
What's wrong?
Control your desires.
That's an old woman. The time isn't right.
I'm going to perform PRU.
Hey.
This is not the time to play politics.
-Isn't PRU…
-It means breathing passage.
I want to see if she's dead or alive.
Good. Yasin is good.
-Let me do my job.
-All right.
Everything he says is good for you.
What's he doing now?
What are you doing, Yasin?
-Thank you.
-Hello?
Yasin.
-What is it, Yasin?
-You got this?
She'll be unconscious
for 1 hour and 26 seconds.
We have time to search for the treasure.
-This is from what you just did?
-Yes.
You. Fat.
Take a rope.
Rope.
-Okay. I'll take a rope.
-Go. Move.
No wonder my old man said
stupidity spreads easily.
I found it!
That's quick.
Okay, let's tie her up. Stand here.
-Hold this.
-Do you come here often?
-You found the rope easily.
-I found it.
Okay. Listen.
Well?
Fat and I will stand guard outside
in case the crazy woman comes back.
Both of you go in,
take the treasure chest, and come out.
-What? Are we the ones going in?
-It's simple, man. Simple.
Okay. Yasin and I will go in.
But don't leave us behind.
-Don't worry.
-I'll never leave you guys.
-Promise?
I promise.
It's dark. Point the light here.
Why is it different?
It's the door.
What's that sound?
Yasin.
A cucumber?
It's a cucumber, Yasin.
A cucumber in a room? Hey, don't.
Good luck.
I'm a vegetarian, Yasin.
Okay.
-Do you want some?
-No, it's okay.
I feel bad for you, Asri.
I'll check this area, Yasin.
Yasin.
-Yasin.
-What?
There's nothing here.
If it's not here, no need to make a fuss.
Don't make a noise. Just relax.
I'm just letting you know.
Even so, don't speak loudly.
Everything all right there?
I think they're okay.
I'm scared. I worry about them, you know.
I'm sure they're okay.
Let's keep standing guard.
Yasin.
There are two chests down here.
-Really?
-There are two chests.
Then you can speak louder. Gosh.
There are two chests down here, Yasin!
That was an example.
Over here, Yasin.
We need to keep calm
in a situation like this.
Where are the chests?
Take them out.
There are two.
It's heavy.
Hold on. Okay.
Three, four.
Yasin.
Is this the one we're looking for?
-One more chest.
-Another one.
It's heavy.
Okay.
Make it upright.
Okay, three, four.
It's heavy.
Hey.
How about the crazy woman
who came to kill us?
I'm very scared.
No way.
Just run.
If she comes here, we'll just run.
You seem to be enjoying that cucumber.
Can we open them?
Focus on this.
How do we open it?
It's not locked, Yasin.
Really?
Open it.
Yasin.
You were right, Yasin.
We're rich. Look at this.
This is real gold.
We're not poor anymore, Yasin.
We're not poor anymore. We're rich, Yasin.
Hey.
If the small chest has this much,
imagine the big one.
This one is a million.
This one is a trillion.
Trillion.
Okay.
They don't even know yet.
Should I open it?
Okay.
Tan Sri *** Yasin, please open it.
I feel embarrassed now.
Tan Sri.
Open it, Tan Sri.
Count for me.
Three, four.
Yasin! What was that?
What happened?
Wait. They look like bones.
I saw them too, Yasin. It's true.
Bones and gold.
Fossil. These are dinosaur bones.
Isn't Fossil a perfume?
No. Not that one.
Fossils are like ancient dinosaur bones,
eggs, and stuff.
If we sell these, they'll be worth a lot.
Really?
Anas?
Yasin.
-A human skeleton and a bracelet.
-Yeah.
Doesn't it look like Anas's…
-ASFATRIYAS!
You're right. The one Anas wears.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
I'm thinking what you're thinking.
Why are you still up?
This place is full of spirits
and you're alone here.
Hey, even if I become a ghost,
I won't be a shrouded ghost.
I'll just be normal.
I want to be friends with you guys.
I think Anas is dead.
He died in this house.
What do you mean?
Fatih.
Anas.
Hey.
Hey, Anas. Yasin.
Come here.
Why is this happening?
What should we do?
What happened? Why did we leave Anas?
Anas is our friend.
No. Don't mention his name again.
Anas is gone.
Anas is dead.
-Seriously, man?
-Yes.
When we went into the room,
there was a chest.
In it, there were bones.
On the bones, there was a bracelet.
It's the same. Ask Yasin.
Anas is the only one
who wears that bracelet.
Impossible.
You don't believe it?
He doesn't believe us, Yasin.
Anas is gone.
What do you need to Google for?
-We saw it ourselves.
-No need.
-What? What is it?
-He's gone.
-He's gone?
-Yasin, Anas isn't in the picture.
-It's true.
He was there, right?
He's a ghost, Yasin. I'm scared, Yasin.
What?
You want to pee?
An ectopic pregnancy?
You can't be pregnant.
What is it then?
What is that?
Your tongue feels bitter?
Is someone behind me?
Right now?
That's Anas, right?
Anas?
Yes, that's Anas.
He's here?
Anas is here!
Why are you here?
Hey. Don't leave me!
He's looking at you!
Don't look at him!
Faster.
We can stand up, Yasin.
Wait for me.
-Come here, Yasin.
-Close the door.
Lock the door.
Hurry up.
Is he still there?
He didn't follow us, right?
We can't climb out of this window either.
Window?
It's closed.
You can still eat in this situation?
Relax.
-The door…
-Don't disturb us.
Go away!
-Why did you come here? Go!
-Yasin, go.
Go ahead, Yasin.
Yasin, Asri, Fat.
-He said my name.
-Open the door. Let me explain.
You can't be trusted.
You're a useless man.
All men are the same!
Hey, what are you saying, Yasin?
Ever since you held my hand,
you've been acting differently.
What am I saying? No.
I'll start saying nonsense
when I'm panicking.
What is this?
What's wrong with you guys?
I'm not dead yet.
How come you're not dead?
You weren't in the picture
when we took a selfie, you know?
Yeah.
I was tying my shoelaces at the time.
I think we should take a selfie
while we wait.
For our friendship. For our memory.
Who knows after we go inside,
someone will die?
Hey, watch your mouth.
You just say whatever you want.
It's just for our memory.
-Our friendship. Come on, man.
-Foul mouth.
Okay. Just do as he says.
-Quickly.
-Selfie, right.
-Use 0.5.
-Move here a bit so I look slimmer.
One.
What about the bracelet then?
Why?
It looks the same, but it's not mine.
What do you mean?
Here's how it goes.
Two years ago, I entered this villa.
-Over here, honey. Check that closet.
-Okay.
Did you find it?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Honey, these items are priceless.
I don't care. I want it.
It's a symbol of our love.
Promise you'll never take
this bracelet off.
For me.
Promise you'll never take
the bracelet off.
Promise?
Promise me.
I promise.
Hey, let her go. Fine, we'll leave.
Honey.
Honey!
That's why I need
brave friends like you guys.
So I can take Laila's corpse
and bury her like any other Muslim.
Am I brave, Yasin?
Yasin!
-What are you doing?
-What are you doing, man?
I want to see if he's human or a ghost.
So is he a ghost or a human?
-Wait a second.
-I'm human.
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
-He feels pain.
-So he's human.
That is our friend.
That's Anas.
So that means
what we're doing is
paranormal work, you know?
Though, honestly,
you all seem far from normal.
Why didn't you tell us the truth?
It would've been easier.
He's crying, Yasin.
-I'm weak at this.
-He's sad, Yasin.
How about this?
Let's go upstairs,
take those bones, and bury them.
That's right, man.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
Thank you, my friends.
Come on.
Wait.
In this situation,
forget about the gloomy stuff.
We want to feel good again.
-Repeat after me.
-How?
-Just repeat after me.
Okay, that's enough.
Now what?
Is that all?
Like Asri said, let's go get those bones.
-Okay, let's go.
-Come on.
Let's go.
-Let's go!
-Yeah.
Hey, don't walk too fast.
I'm not brave enough yet.
-Come on. Hurry.
-Anas.
Come on, Anas.
Hurry.
Let's just leave this house, man.
Hurry up.
Yasin!
-That crazy woman is gone, Yasin.
-It's okay.
-Where did she go, Yasin?
-She's gone.
We need to keep calm
in a situation like this.
But if that woman is gone,
we can't stay calm.
Seriously? Should we stay calm or not?
Run!
Open the door, Nas.
-I can't.
-It's locked.
Ma'am, have you seen the door keys?
No one can leave this house.
Get the tool from my pants pocket, Nas.
You'll die just like
the owner of this house.
Not that tool.
No one has ever touched it before.
Ma'am, please.
You'll die just like
the owner of this house.
I took good care of them.
I fed them, but they were cruel.
They tortured me.
-They tortured me!
-Really?
-I felt satisfied!
-Satisfied?
I chopped up their bodies one by one.
Open the door!
Open it!
-Hey, woman. Open the door now.
-Open it, madwoman.
-Open the door right now!
-I'll break the house.
-Open the door!
-You ignore me on purpose.
-Open it!
-Open the door!
-Do you think your meals are free?
-Open the door now!
-I'll break it!
What does it have to do with us?
I'm satisfied.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, that's enough.
The door of repentance is still open.
And Yasin can open this door.
You're not in my shoes.
Why would you be in your shoes?
This house is big.
This ghost is dumb.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, calm down.
Listen. God still loves you.
The greater the test,
the closer He is to you.
-Silence!
-It's stated in the hadith.
Ma'am?
Ma'am.
Yasin. Fat.
Yasin!
Did you just hit her head like that?
Yasin, she's an old woman.
Where are your manners?
What are you doing, man?
You should've waited
until she finished talking.
Wait until she finished talking?
Bring her back then.
Make a WhatsApp group.
I just saved your lives.
Is she dead?
But ghosts are already dead, right?
Hey, I'm going to grab my bag.
-What do we do now?
-Anas, wait for me.
Oh my god.
Finally, it's over.
Our mission is done, right?
Don't ever invite me here again, okay?
Alhamdulillah.
Oh my god.
This is the first time I heard
a robber say, "Alhamdulillah."
I can't be saying, "Abdullah."
-Gosh.
-You're right.
But we're not that bad.
Hey.
Anas.
What's done is done. It's all over.
What's wrong, man?
Nas.
You should know
what you did today was a good thing.
Today, you've freed
this soul from torment.
You've returned this soul to the Creator.
That's right, man.
Our love and affection can't compare
to the love of our Creator.
Isn't that right?
-Yes.
-That's right.
Yeah.
That's good.
Thank you, my friends.
Yeah, it's okay.
It's okay.
You don't have to thank us.
What we did today
wasn't a sacrifice, but a responsibility.
Because we're not just friends.
I see you as my own family.
Family always sticks together.
-Right?
-Yes.
-That's nice.
-I agree.
You, you, and you are not my friends.
Yasin.
Yasin, what's wrong with you?
You're all a part of me.
You made me anxious.
That's why, from today onward,
there's one thing we can learn.
No matter what happens,
we have to take care of our friendship.
I know this part.
-You remember, right? It's simple.
-Come on.
You remember, right?
Anas.
Keep those bones away from me.
Three, four.
-ASFA…
-ASPARAGUS!
You got it wrong.
Who's Gus? It's Yas.
-ASFA…
-Yasin. Yas.
Yasin.
Nas. Yas. Nas. You…
Okay, let's do it again. ASFATRIYAS.
Ready. Three, four.
-ASFATRIYAS!
Let's go, Anas.
Hey, who's driving?
Let's go. Okay.
All right.
Everything's settled.
If there's nothing else, I'm heading back.
Okay.
Wait a moment. Relax.
We've buried the bones. It's fine now.
But if you're really sad,
we'll bury you too.
If anything happens, just give me a call.
-Alhamdulillah.
-All right. See you again.
We got what we wanted, Nas.
-Bye.
-Thank you for helping me.
-Okay.
-Call us if anything.
-Bye.
-Thank you.
We still have the car, right?
So fast.
Over here.
Hey, idiot.
MOUNT STONG
Why are you driving like a maniac?
Hurry up, guys.
We're still alive!
-Hurry up.
-Hurry.
My treasure.
-Come on.
-Applause!
You're truly brilliant, Yasin.
Hey, help me out.
You have big bones. Lift the chest.
I'll help close it.
Put it up there.
Open it.
Look around first.
-Make sure this area is safe.
-Coast is clear.
It's clear.
-Wait.
-What?
Why must it be here?
Here, it's so hot, you know.
I want to show you something shiny.
Lighting. I know, Yasin.
-Open it.
We're rich!
In honor of Mount Stong,
we can get stoned after this.
Let's take it.
-Let's split it.
-This one.
It's heavy.
I can't believe this.
Be patient. Return it.
Let's divide it equally.
Give it back.
Please.
-You take one. I'll take one box.
-We have to do the math.
It'll be settled, Yasin.
Hold out your hands.
-This is for you.
-What about me?
-I got one.
-This is for me.
-One more.
-One more for you.
-That's fair.
One more for you.
How many of us are here?
Three. Two, three. Anas isn't here.
Three.
Beside me?
Is it beside me?
You won't get away.
Forever!